goedekers.com 2010-09-15

# Privacy Policy - Home Appliances, Mattresses and Electronics from Number1Direct.

**Privacy Policy**

Goedeker Television Co. Inc. respects your privacy and has created this Privacy Statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to customer privacy. We have established this Statement as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices to our customers and visitors. This Privacy Statement describes how we use, disclose and protect the personally identifiable information that enables us to identify you, such as your name, and email address. By using this Site, you agree to this Privacy Statement.

Goedeker Television Co. Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build users trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This Privacy Statement covers the site [www.Number1Direct.com](http://www.number1direct.com/). Because this Site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [sales@Number1Direct.com](mailto:sales@Number1Direct.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaints.php> . TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

**Service Providers**

We use a third party to host the shopping cart on our Site and associated account pages. When you purchase a product from our Site, we request your billing address and your financial information to fulfill your payment. We also collect your name, phone number and email address when you request information from us regarding our products to service your request. We use third parties to process payments you submit on our Site. We also use a third party shipping agent with whom we share your shipping address to deliver the products you purchase on our Site.

These Service Providers are not authorized to use your personal information for any of their own promotional purposes or any other purposes beyond fulfilling the service request for which we have shared your personal information with them. Number1Direct by Goedekers does not share your personal information with any third parties for their promotional purposes.

**Cookies**

When you interact with this Site, we try to make that experience simple and meaningful. We use cookies on this Site. When you visit our Site, our web server sends a cookie to your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a computers hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies are used to indicate whether you have visited the Site previously. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. If you reject cookies, you will still be able to use our Site, but may not have access to all the Site preference information that a cookie allows us to tailor your user experience on our Site.

Third Party Cookies: From time to time we may engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to our Site to assist us in administering and improving the quality of our Site and services to you. Some of these third parties may use cookies on our site to help track visitor behavior. We have no access to or control over these cookies. Such cookies are not used to associate individual website visitors’ personally identifiable information.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update, delete, or deactivate by emailing us at [sales@Number1Direct.com](mailto:sales@Number1Direct.com). You can also access your information provided to us during registration by signing into your account on our Site and editing your information and preferences.

Number1Direct by Goedeker's does send users administrative, order confirmation, and service related emails which given that they’re not promotional in nature, cannot be opted out of.

From time to time, we shall send users product information we believe would be of interest to them via email. If you no longer wish to receive these emails from us, you can “opt out” by selecting the “Unsubscribe” link that shall be present on each email we send.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. This is why we also use additional security measures and services such as McAfee SECURE® services to provide the latest in additional securities, scanning the Site every day. At Number 1 Direct by Goedeker's, we care about your Security!

If you have any questions about security on our web site, you can send an email to us at [sales@Number1Direct.com](mailto:sales@Number1Direct.com)

**Business Transitions**

In the event Number1Direct by Goedekers goes through a business transition, such as a sale, merger, or acquisition by another company your personally identifiable information will likely be among the transferred assets. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our web site for 30 days in such an event so that you can make a choice about how your information is used.

**Legal Disclosure**

We may be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or to third parties under certain circumstances, such as illegal activity on our Site. We reserve the right to release personal information to our Service Providers, law enforcement or other government officials or in response to a formal request in a civil action, judicial proceeding or court order.

**Changes in the Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and any other places on the Site we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstance, if any, we disclose it. In the event that we make a material change to the way we use the personally identifiable information you’ve submitted on our Site, we shall notify you via a prominent notice on our Site as well as by email.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, Please contact us at:

[sales@Number1Direct.com](mailto:sales@Number1Direct.com) or [www.Number1Direct.com](http://www.number1appliance.com/)

**Goedeker's Superstore**  
13850 Manchester Rd.  
Ballwin, MO 63011
